https://zvulony.ca/law-articles/privacy-law/

Privacy LawYou are here: Home1 / Articles by our Lawyers2 / Privacy LawPrivacy Law ArticlesArticles about privacy law in Canada
Your Questions Answered
Do you have questions or concerns about a privacy law issue? Our Toronto privacy lawyer can help!
Ask a Privacy Lawyer
Privacy and Health RecordsGil Zvulony discusses unlawful disclosure of private health records and privacy breaches in hospitals.February 26, 2015/by Gil ZvulonyCan you opt out of Facebook’s Terms of Use?Can you protect your intellectual property and private information from Facebook by updating your status with certain legal language?December 4, 2014/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Breaches Are Usually Not Worth Much MoneyMost minor privacy breaches will fall in the realm of small claims court jurisdiction.November 11, 2014/by Gil ZvulonyUser Based Insurance and PrivacyGil Zvulony was a panelist at the Telematics Canada Conference 2014.June 25, 2014/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy, Tracking Devices, & Usage Based Auto InsuranceToronto Privacy Lawyer, Gil Zvulony, recently discussed potential privacy concerns regarding the use of tracking devices used by some auto insurance companies.March 14, 2014/by Gil ZvulonyLegal Rights in a PhotographToronto internet lawyer Gil Zvulony examines the various rights in a photograph, including, copyrights, moral rights, publicity rights and privacy rights.
He discusses the rights of photographers, models, by-standers, celebrities, and of ordinary people.March 6, 2014/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Law: An OverviewA discussion of various options open to victims of privacy breaches.December 10, 2012/by Gil ZvulonyIn the News – Using Technology to Track your Cheating PartnerToronto Internet Lawyer Shaya Silber's opinion was recently sought by City TV with respect to the legality of using technology to track your cheating partner.September 4, 2012/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Law and the Workplace: Job ApplicationsEmployers have access to unprecedented amounts of information on their employees and job candidates. Many people, especially young people, don’t realize how much information they are publishing about themselves, and what the possible implications are.June 4, 2012/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Law: Intrusion Upon SeclusionPrivacy law in Ontario has expanded to include the new tort of Intrusion Upon Seclusion.May 2, 2012/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Law: Google and PIPEDAChanges to Google’s privacy policy in March 2012 has raised many questions.May 2, 2012/by Gil ZvulonyIn the News: Our Internet Lawyer Quoted in the Toronto StarOur Toronto Internet lawyer's opinion was recently featured in a Toronto Star article about a new Facebook feature to prevent suicide.December 18, 2011/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Law: License PlatesToronto Privacy Lawyer discusses the privacy law implications of the collection and storage of license plate data by businesses.April 28, 2011/by Gil ZvulonyCloud Computing: Everyone is Doing it!The use of cloud computing is growing.
This article looks at the legal and privacy implications of cloud computing for businesses.April 27, 2011/by Gil ZvulonyPrivacy Policy: Why Your Website Should Have OneToronto Privacy lawyer discusses the advantages of having a privacy policy in place for your website.January 24, 2011/by Gil ZvulonyProtecting your Private Information in OntarioAs we move forward into an age where growing portions of lives are becoming increasingly digitized, many holes are becoming apparent in these new information systems. A lot of these holes revolve around issues of personal information and privacy. Because this scenario is relatively novel, many people including policy makers, academics, lawyers and so on, are grappling with the consequences; and more importantly, with avenues by which to remedy apparent wrongs.January 24, 2011/by Gil ZvulonyAre Browse Wrap (Terms of Use) Agreements Binding?It is increasingly common for websites to include “Terms of Use” agreements. These agreements set out the terms and conditions to which the user must agree in exchange for using the site. A question that sometimes arises in the law is: how does one demonstrate that a user assented to the Terms of Use agreement?November 29, 2010/by Gil Zvulony
416-483-3500
Ask a Toronto Privacy Lawyer
Ask Gil Zvulony, a Toronto Privacy Lawyer
Ask a Lawyer with
expertise
experience
knowledge
Consult a Toronto Lawyer with Expertise in Privacy Law
Ask a Privacy Lawyer
Search
Home
About Zvulony & Co.
Consult a Lawyer
Contact Us
Lawyers in Toronto, Canada Zvulony & Co., P.C.
28 Finch Ave West
Suite 208
Toronto,
ON
Canada
M2N 2G7
416.483.3500 | 1.888.691.8114
Legal Disclaimer The presentation of information on this website is NOT individualized legal advice and should not be relied on as such.
Articles are intended to offer general comments on legal developments of concern to individuals, business and legal professionals and are not intended to provide legal opinions. Readers should seek legal advice on the particular issues that concern them.
Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
2002-2020 All Rights Reserved
Zvulony & Co. P.C., Toronto, Ontario, Canada
Scroll to top
